https://bristolcase.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to main contentCall (585) 768-7000 Email Us 8715 Lake Rd. LeRoy, NY 14482AboutCase StudyCasesCustom CasesShipping CasesRack CasesPelican CasesSKB CasesPlasticaseInsertsContactPrivacy PolicyNovember 13, 2017This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for bristolcase.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.UpdatesOur Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 585-786-7000 or info@bristolcase.com.Custom QuoteCustom Quote
If you are human, leave this field blank. Name & ContactDescribe Your ProjectName & ContactDescribe Your
Project Name *
Email *
Phone *
Budget *
What is Your Budget? Less than $500 $500-$750 $750-1,250 $1,250 - $1,750 Unsure, let's talk
Quantity *
How Many Cases Will You Need? 1-5 5-9 10-19 20+
Timeline *
Select Your Timeline ... This Year This Quarter This Month Not sure, let's talk
What Do You Need * PreviousNext reCAPTCHA
SubmitORCON FAMILY OF PRODUCTS
Sustainable Packaging Solutions
Biodegradable-Protective Packaging
Custom Cases Design
Call (585) 768-7000 Email Us 8715 Lake Rd. LeRoy, NY 14482AboutBristol Case has been manufacturing custom cases designed to fit your needs since 1974! If you travel with valuable equipment, you may need the maximum protection that Bristol Case can provide.SubscribeSubscribe
If you are human, leave this field blank.
Name *
Email *
reCAPTCHA
SubmitLocation © 2020 Bristol Case. All rights reserved. Privacy PolicyDesigned and developed by
